[{"question":". %u8BF7%u9009%u62E9%u6B63%u786E%u76F8%u673A%u56FE%u4F20%u6A21%u5757%u7684%u63A5%u6536%u7AEF ID %u8BBE%u7F6E%u6B65%u9AA4%u987A%u5E8F<br><br>a. %u4F7F%u7528USB Type-C %u6570%u636E%u7EBF%u5C06PC %u548C%u63A5%u6536%u7AEF%u7684USB %u7AEF%u53E3%u8FDE%u63A5%uFF0C%u5C06%u76F8%u673A%u56FE%u4F20%u6A21%u5757%u63A5%u6536%u7AEF%u7528%u7535%u6E90%u9002%u914D%u5668%u4F9B%u7535%uFF0C<br>%u7B49%u5F8520 %u79D2%u5DE6%u53F3%u76F4%u5230%u72B6%u6001%u6307%u793A%u706F%u4E3A%u7EFF%u8272%u5E38%u4EAE%uFF0C%u8868%u793A%u542F%u52A8%u5B8C%u6210%u3002<br><br>b.%u6253%u5F00PC %u7684%u8BBE%u5907%u7BA1%u7406%u5668%uFF0C%u5C55%u5F00%u7F51%u7EDC%u9002%u914D%u5668%u5B50%u83DC%u5355%uFF0C%u68C0%u67E5%u662F%u5426%u6709%u201CRemote NDIS based Internet Sharing<br>Device%u201D%u8BBE%u5907%uFF0C%u5982%u679C%u6CA1%u6709%u5B89%u88C5%u9A71%u52A8%u9700%u8981%u53C2%u8003%u201C%u6FC0%u6D3B%u63A5%u6536%u7AEF%u201D%u7AE0%u8282%u5B89%u88C5%u63A5%u6536%u7AEF%u6A21%u5757DJI Phantom 4 Drivers_1.2_Installer %u9A71%u52A8%u3002<br><br>c. %u6253%u5F00%u201CRoboMaster Client%u201D%uFF0C%u70B9%u51FB%u201C%u8FDB%u5165%u5BA2%u6237%u7AEF%u201D%u6309%u94AE%uFF0C%u8FDB%u5165%u5BA2%u6237%u7AEF%u753B%u9762%uFF0C%u5728%u5BA2%u6237%u7AEF%u754C%u9762%u6309%u7535%u8111%u952E%u76D8%u4E0A%u7684%u201Cp%u201D%u952E%u5F39%u51FA%u201C%u8BBE%u7F6E%u9762%u677F%u201D%u5B50%u9875%u9762%uFF0C%u5728%u201C%u767B%u9646%u201D%u83DC%u5355%u7684%u4E0B%u62C9%u6846%u9009%u62E9%u63A5%u6536<br>%u7AEF%u5BF9%u5E94%u7684%u673A%u5668%u4EBAID%uFF0C%u5BA2%u6237%u7AEF%u8F6F%u4EF6%u4F1A%u81EA%u52A8%u8BBE%u7F6E%u63A5%u6536%u7AEF%u7684%u56FE%u4F20%u901A%u9053ID%u3002<br><br>d. %u5728%u8BBE%u7F6E%u9762%u677F%u7684%u4E0B%u65B9%u53EF%u4EE5%u770B%u5230%u56FE%u4F20%u72B6%u6001%uFF1A%u4E32%u53E3%uFF0C%u8FDE%u63A5%u72B6%u6001%uFF0C%u901F%u7387%uFF0C%u6A21%u5F0F%u548C%u901A%u9053%uFF0C%u5206%u522B%u8868%u793A%u63A5%u6536%u7AEF%u4E32%u53E3%u7684<br>%u8FDE%u63A5%u72B6%u6001%u3001%u56FE%u4F20%u7684%u8FDE%u63A5%u72B6%u6001%u3001%u4F20%u8F93%u901F%u7387%u3001%u5DE5%u4F5C%u6A21%u5F0F%u548C%u56FE%u4F20%u901A%u9053ID%u3002<br><br>e.  %u63A5%u6536%u7AEF%u6536%u5230%u56FE%u4F20%u901A%u9053ID %u540E%uFF0C%u4F1A%u81EA%u52A8%u8DDF%u76F8%u540C%u56FE%u4F20%u901A%u9053ID %u7684%u53D1%u9001%u7AEF%u5BF9%u9891%uFF0C%u5BF9%u9891%u6210%u529F%u540E%u5BA2%u6237%u7AEF%u4F1A%u663E%u793A%u56FE%u4F20<br>%u4F20%u56DE%u7684%u753B%u9762%uFF0C%u540C%u65F6%u5BA2%u6237%u7AEF%u8BBE%u7F6E%u9762%u677F%u7684%u56FE%u4F20%u8FDE%u63A5%u72B6%u6001%u6307%u793A%u706F%u4F1A%u53D8%u6210%u7EFF%u8272<br><br><br><br><br>","answer":"abcde"},{"question":". %u4EE5%u4E0B%u90A3%u4E00%u9879%u529F%u80FD%u662FRoboMaster%u670D%u52A1%u5668%u4E0D%u80FD%u5B9E%u73B0%u7684","answer":"%u4E3A%u88C1%u5224%u7CFB%u7EDF%u6A21%u5757%u5347%u7EA7"},{"question":". %u5173%u4E8E%u4E3B%u63A7%u6A21%u5757%u7684%u5B89%u88C5%u65B9%u5F0F%u63CF%u8FF0%u6B63%u786E%u7684%u662F%uFF1F<br>%u2460%u5207%u52FF%u906E%u6321%u5347%u7EA7%u63A5%u53E3<br>%u2461%u53EF%u4EE5%u906E%u6321%u7EA2%u5916%u63A5%u6536%u5668<br>%u2462%u4E3A%u4E86%u8FDB%u884C%u4FDD%u62A4%uFF0C%u4F7F%u7528%u91D1%u5C5E%u76D2%u5B50%u5C01%u95ED%u4FDD%u62A4%u4E3B%u63A7%u6A21%u5757<br>%u2463%u5B89%u88C5%u65F6%u9700%u8981%u8003%u8651%u64CD%u4F5C%u4FBF%u6613%u6027%uFF0C%u4FDD%u8BC1%u5C4F%u5E55%u548C%u6309%u952E%u6CA1%u6709%u906E%u6321","answer":"%u2460%u2463"},{"question":". %u6839%u636E%u4E0B%u56FE%u4E3B%u63A7%u6A21%u5757%u5C4F%u5E55%u663E%u793A%u80FD%u83B7%u53D6%u7684%u6B63%u786E%u4FE1%u606F%u6709%uFF1F<img src=\"http://hz-platinic-data-prod.oss-cn-hangzhou.aliyuncs.com/f220bdf1-9dfb-4beb-adf5-358e33f33e6f\">","answer":"%u670911%u4E2A%u6A21%u5757%u5904%u4E8E%u79BB%u7EBF%u6216%u8005%u6545%u969C%u72B6%u6001"},{"question":". %u5728%u4F7F%u7528%u5347%u7EA7%u5DE5%u5177%u8FDB%u884C%u5347%u7EA7%u65F6%uFF0C%u53D1%u73B0%u5347%u7EA7%u6309%u94AE%u4E3A%u7070%u8272%u65E0%u6CD5%u70B9%u51FB%uFF0C%u6309F5%u5237%u65B0%u540E%u72B6%u6001%u4E0D%u53D8%uFF0C%u5219%u53EF%u80FD%u662F%u4EC0%u4E48%u539F%u56E0%u5BFC%u81F4%u7684","answer":"%u8BE5%u6A21%u5757%u56FA%u4EF6%u7248%u672C%u5DF2%u662F%u6700%u65B0%uFF0C%u4E0D%u9700%u8981%u5347%u7EA7"},{"question":". %u573A%u5730%u4EA4%u4E92%u6A21%u5757%u4F7F%u7528%u6CE8%u610F%u4E8B%u9879%u6709%uFF1F<br>%u2460%u4F7F%u7528%u65F6%u8BF7%u786E%u4FDD%u7535%u8DEF%u65E0%u77ED%u8DEF%u3001%u63A5%u53E3%u6309%u7167%u8981%u6C42%u6B63%u786E%u8FDE%u63A5<br>%u2461%u8FDB%u884CID%u8BBE%u7F6E%u540E%u4F7F%u7528<br>%u2462%u786E%u4FDD%u5F85%u68C0%u6D4B%u7684IC%u5361%u4E24%u9762%u5747%u65E0%u91D1%u5C5E%u906E%u6321%uFF0C%u5426%u5219%u5C06%u4F1A%u5F71%u54CD%u4EA4%u4E92%u6A21%u5757%u7684%u6709%u6548%u68C0%u6D4B%u8DDD%u79BB<br>%u2463%u4EA4%u4E92%u6A21%u5757%u9700%u914D%u5408%u88C1%u5224%u7CFB%u7EDF%u4E3B%u63A7%u6A21%u5757%u4EE5%u53CA%u7535%u6E90%u7BA1%u7406%u6A21%u5757%u4E00%u540C%u4F7F%u7528","answer":"%u2460%u2461%u2462%u2463"},{"question":". %u901A%u8FC7%u4EA4%u4E92%u754C%u9762%uFF0C%u673A%u5668%u4EBA%u7AEF%u53EF%u4EE5%u9009%u62E9%u9884%u5148%u914D%u7F6E%u7684SSID%uFF08%u5373WIFI%u7684%u540D%u5B57%uFF09%u4E0E%u670D%u52A1%u5668%u5EFA%u7ACB%u8FDE%u63A5%u5E76%u901A%u4FE1%uFF0C%u64CD%u4F5C%u4E0D%u6B63%u786E%u7684%u662F%uFF1F","answer":"%u5728%u6B63%u786E%u64CD%u4F5C\"Scan SSID\"%u540E%uFF0C%u9009%u62E9%u76EE%u7684SSID%uFF0C%u77ED%u6309%u5373%u53EF%u8FDE%u63A5%u5230WiFi%uFF0C%u540C%u65F6%u4F1A%u8BB0%u4F4FSSID%u3002%u4E0B%u6B21%u5F00%u673A%uFF0C%u673A%u5668%u4EBA%u7AEF%u4F1A%u81EA%u52A8%u8FDE%u63A5%u8BE5SSID"},{"question":". %u7B2C%u4E00%u6B21%u5B89%u88C5%u5B8C%u6210%u4E0A%u7535%uFF0C%u5BFC%u81F4%u88C1%u5224%u7CFB%u7EDF%u4E3B%u63A7%u6A21%u5757%u663E%u793A%u6A21%u5757%u5F02%u5E38%u60C5%u51B5%u6709%uFF1F<br>%u2460%u901A%u8FC7%u7535%u6E90%u7BA1%u7406%u6A21%u5757%u7684%u4E91%u53F0%u4F9B%u7535%u63A5%u53E3%u7ED9%u673A%u5668%u4EBA%u4E91%u53F0%u4F9B%u7535<br>%u2461%u88C5%u7532%u6A21%u5757ID%u6CA1%u6709%u6B63%u786E%u8BBE%u7F6E<br>%u2462%u573A%u5730%u4EA4%u4E92%u6A21%u5757%u6709%u6548%u8DDD%u79BB%u5185%u5B58%u5728RFID%u5361<br>%u2463%u5C04%u901F%u6A21%u5757%u6709%u5F02%u7269%u906E%u6321%u4F20%u611F%u5668","answer":"%u2461%u2463"},{"question":". %u4EE5%u4E0B%u54EA%u9879%u5173%u4E8E%u4E3B%u63A7%u6A21%u5757%u6309%u952E%u529F%u80FD%u63CF%u8FF0%u4E0D%u6B63%u786E%u7684%u662F%uFF1F","answer":"%u5728%u4E3B%u9875%u9762%u65F6%uFF0C%u957F%u6309%u53D6%u6D88%u952E%u4F1A%u8FDB%u5165%u5B9E%u65F6%u4FE1%u606F%u663E%u793A%u9875%u9762"},{"question":". 17mm%u4E0E42mm%u6D4B%u901F%u6A21%u5757%u7684%u6D4B%u901F%u8303%u56F4%u5206%u522B%u662F%u591A%u5C11%uFF1F","answer":"1-50m/s; 1-30m/s"},{"question":". %u73B0%u5728%u9700%u8981%u5C06%u673A%u5668%u4EBA%u67E5%u8BE2%u88C5%u7532%u6A21%u5757%u7248%u672C%uFF0C%u4E0B%u9762%u6B63%u786E%u7684%u8BBE%u7F6E%u987A%u5E8F%u5E94%u8BE5%u662F%uFF1F<br>a.%u4E3B%u9875%u9762%u957F%u6309%u786E%u8BA4%u952E%uFF0C%u901A%u8FC7%u4E0A%u7FFB%u4E0B%u7FFB%u6309%u952E%u9009%u62E9\"Read Version\"<br>b.%u901A%u8FC7%u4E0A%u7FFB%u4E0B%u7FFB%u6309%u952E%u67E5%u770B%u5404%u4E2A%u88C5%u7532%u6A21%u5757%u7684%u7248%u672C%u53F7<br>c.%u901A%u8FC7%u4E0A%u7FFB%u4E0B%u7FFB%u6309%u952E%u9009%u62E9\"Armor Module\"%uFF0C%u77ED%u6309%u786E%u8BA4%u952E%u8FDB%u884C%u67E5%u8BE2","answer":"acb"},{"question":". %u4EE5%u4E0B%u54EA%u9879%u5173%u4E8E%u4E3B%u63A7%u6A21%u5757%u4E2D%u6D4B%u901F%u6A21%u5757%u8BBE%u7F6E%u63CF%u8FF0%u6B63%u786E%u7684%u662F%uFF1F<br>%u2460%u989D%u5916%u5C04%u901F%u6A21%u5757%u8BBE%u7F6E%u7684%u9009%u9879\"Ext Setup Mon\"%u5C5E%u4E8E\"Debug Option\"%u5B50%u9879%u76EE<br>%u2461%u5728\"Module Setup\"%u9875%u9762%u4E0B%uFF0C%u9009%u62E9%u201CCompass Calibration%u201D%u53EF%u4EE5%u5BF9%u6D4B%u901F%u6A21%u5757%u4E0A%u7684%u6307%u5357%u9488%u8FDB%u884C%u6821%u51C6<br>%u2462%u5728\"Module Setup\"%u9875%u9762%u4E0B%uFF0C%u9009%u62E9%u201CCompass Calibration%u201D%uFF0C%u82E5%u6B63%u786E%u8FDE%u63A5%u5C04%u901F%u6A21%u5757%uFF0C%u5219%u6D4B%u901F%u6A21%u5757%u4FA7%u9762LED%u9AD8%u4EAE%u8868%u793A%u8FDB%u5165%u6821%u51C6%u6A21%u5F0F<br>%u2463%u5728%u5C04%u901F%u6A21%u5757%u8FDB%u5165%u6821%u51C6%u72B6%u6001%u540E%uFF0C%u5C06%u5C04%u901F%u6A21%u5757%u6309%u7167%u4E0A%u3001%u4E0B%u3001%u524D%u3001%u540E%u3001%u5DE6%u3001%u53F3%u516D%u4E2A%u65B9%u5411%u9759%u6B62%u653E%u7F6E%u4E00%u6BB5%u65F6%u95F4%uFF082s%u5DE6%u53F3%uFF09%u5373%u53EF%u5B8C%u6210%u6821%u51C6<br>","answer":"%u2460%u2461"},{"question":". %u73B0%u5728%u9700%u8981%u5C06%u673A%u5668%u4EBA%u8FDE%u63A5%u4E0A%u65E0%u7EBF%u7F51%u7EDC%uFF0C%u4E0B%u9762%u6B63%u786E%u7684%u8BBE%u7F6E%u987A%u5E8F%u5E94%u8BE5%u662F%uFF1F<br>a.%u901A%u8FC7%u4E0A%u7FFB%u4E0B%u7FFB%u6309%u952E%u9009%u62E9\"Scan SSID\"%uFF0C%u77ED%u6309%u786E%u8BA4%u952E<br>b.%u4E3B%u9875%u9762%u957F%u6309%u786E%u8BA4%u952E%uFF0C%u901A%u8FC7%u4E0A%u7FFB%u4E0B%u7FFB%u6309%u952E%u9009%u62E9\"WIFI Setup\"%uFF0C%u77ED%u6309%u786E%u8BA4%u952E%u8FDB%u5165<br>c.%u901A%u8FC7%u4E0A%u7FFB%u4E0B%u7FFB%u6309%u952E%u9009%u62E9%u5408%u9002%u7684SSID%uFF0C%u77ED%u6309%u786E%u8BA4%u952E%u8FDB%u884C%u8FDE%u63A5","answer":"bac"},{"question":". %u5728%u4E3A%u88C1%u5224%u7CFB%u7EDF%u5347%u7EA7%u65F6%uFF0C%u5982%u4F55%u83B7%u53D6%u5404%u4E2A%u6A21%u5757%u6700%u65B0%u7684%u56FA%u4EF6","answer":"%u5728RMTool%u8F6F%u4EF6%u4E2D%u70B9%u51FB%u4E0B%u8F7D%u56FA%u4EF6%u6765%u83B7%u53D6%u6700%u65B0%u56FA%u4EF6"},{"question":". %u5982%u4F55%u83B7%u5F97%u6700%u65B0%u7248%u7684%u5347%u7EA7%u5DE5%u5177%u548C%u670D%u52A1%u5668%u8F6F%u4EF6%uFF1F","answer":"%u5728RoboMaster%u5B98%u7F51%u4E0A%u4E0B%u8F7D"},{"question":". %u6821%u51C6%u6D4B%u901F%u6A21%u5757%u78C1%u529B%u8BA1%u65F6%uFF0C%u64CD%u4F5CUI%u540E%uFF0C%u8FDB%u884C%u4EC0%u4E48%u64CD%u4F5C%uFF1F","answer":"%u5C06%u6D4B%u901F%u6A21%u5757%u6C34%u5E73%u65CB%u8F6C360%u5EA6%uFF0C%u7136%u540E%u5C06%u67AA%u7BA1%u7AD6%u76F4%u671D%u4E0A%uFF0C%u5E76%u6CBF%u7740%u67AA%u7BA1%u65B9%u5411%u65CB%u8F6C360°"},{"question":". %u4EE5%u4E0B%u54EA%u9879%u5173%u4E8E%u4E3B%u63A7%u6A21%u5757%u4E2D%u8BFB%u53D6%u5404%u6A21%u5757%u7248%u672C%u63CF%u8FF0%u6B63%u786E%u7684%u662F%uFF1F","answer":"%u6BCF%u6B21%u53EA%u80FD%u8BFB%u53D6%u4E00%u79CD%u6A21%u5757%u7684%u7248%u672C"},{"question":". %u4EE5%u4E0B%u5BF9%u4E8E%u88C5%u7532%u6A21%u5757%u7684%u4F7F%u7528%u63CF%u8FF0%u6B63%u786E%u7684%u4E00%u9879%u662F","answer":"%u88C5%u7532%u6A21%u5757%u5728%u4F7F%u7528%u524D%u9700%u8981%u68C0%u67E5%u662F%u5426%u5B58%u5728ID%u51B2%u7A81%u7684%u60C5%u51B5"},{"question":". %u4EE5%u4E0B%u54EA%u9879%u5173%u4E8E%u4E3B%u63A7%u6A21%u5757%u4E2D%u88C5%u7532ID%u8BBE%u7F6E%u63CF%u8FF0%u4E0D%u6B63%u786E%u7684%u662F%uFF1F","answer":"%u5728\"Module Setup\"%u9875%u9762%u4E0B%uFF0C%u77ED%u6309\"Armor ID 0\"%uFF0C%u5219%u4F1A%u628A%u6B64%u65F6%u8FDE%u63A5%u5230%u4E3B%u63A7%u6A21%u5757%u7684%u6240%u6709%u88C5%u7532%u6A21%u5757%u7684ID%u8BBE%u7F6E%u4E3A0%u53F7"},{"question":". %u6D4B%u901F%u6A21%u5757%u7684%u4F9B%u7535%u7535%u538B%u4E3A%u591A%u5C11%uFF1F","answer":"12V"},{"question":". %u88C1%u5224%u7CFB%u7EDF%u7528%u6237%u63A5%u53E3%u8F93%u51FA%u7684%u6570%u636E%u4E0D%u5305%u542B%u6709","answer":"%u654C%u65B9%u673A%u5668%u4EBA%u4F4D%u7F6E"},{"question":". %u88C1%u5224%u7CFB%u7EDF%u5728%u7EC4%u4EF6WIFI%u5C40%u57DF%u7F51%u65F6%uFF0C%u6240%u9009AP%u7684%u65E0%u7EBF%u9891%u6BB5%u5E94%u4E3A%u4EE5%u4E0B%u54EA%u4E00%u4E2A","answer":"2.4G"},{"question":". %u673A%u5668%u4EBA%u7AEF%u5B89%u88C5%u5B8C%u6210%u540E%uFF0C%u9700%u8981%u68C0%u67E5%u5B89%u5168%u76F8%u5173%u4E8B%u9879%uFF0C%u4EE5%u4E0B%u54EA%u9879%u4E0D%u6B63%u786E%uFF1F","answer":"%u4E3B%u63A7%u6A21%u5757%u7684USB%u53E3%u7ED9%u5176%u4ED6%u6A21%u5757%u4F9B%u7535"},{"question":". %u5728%u6D4B%u901F%u6A21%u5757%u4E2D%uFF0C%u4EE5%u4E0B%u8BF4%u6CD5%u4E2D%u6B63%u786E%u7684%u662F%u54EA%u4E2A%uFF1F","answer":"%u6D4B%u901F%u6A21%u5757%u7EA2%u5916%u5BF9%u7BA1%u68C0%u6D4B%u5F02%u5E38%u65F6%uFF0C%u4E24%u4FA7LED%u706F%u7EA2%u84DD%u706F%u4EA4%u66FF%u95EA%u70C1%u3002"},{"question":". %u5728%u706F%u6761%u6A21%u5757%u4E2D%uFF0C%u8BF4%u6CD5%u9519%u8BEF%u7684%u662F%u54EA%u4E2A%uFF1F","answer":"%u706F%u6761%u6A21%u5757%u4F9B%u7535%u7535%u538B%u4E3A24V"},{"question":". %u5982%u679C%u53D1%u73B0RoboMaster%u88C1%u5224%u7CFB%u7EDF%u5BA2%u6237%u7AEF%u65E0%u6CD5%u8FDE%u63A5%u5230%u670D%u52A1%u5668%uFF0C%u5219%u4E0D%u53EF%u80FD%u662F%u4EE5%u4E0B%u54EA%u4E00%u79CD%u60C5%u51B5%u5BFC%u81F4%u7684","answer":"%u673A%u5668%u4EBA%u6CA1%u6709%u8FDE%u63A5%u5230%u670D%u52A1%u5668"},{"question":". %u5728%u7535%u6E90%u7BA1%u7406%u6A21%u5757%u4E2D%uFF0C%u4EE5%u4E0B%u8BF4%u6CD5%u9519%u8BEF%u7684%u662F%uFF1F","answer":"%u7535%u6E90%u7BA1%u7406%u6A21%u5757%u53EF%u4E3A%u5E95%u76D8%u3001%u4E91%u53F0%u3001%u53D1%u5C04%u673A%u6784%u548CMini PC%u63D0%u4F9B24V%u76F4%u6D41%u7535%u6E90%u8F93%u51FA%uFF0C%u5E76%u68C0%u6D4B%u8FD94%u4E2A%u901A%u9053%u7684%u7535%u6D41%u3001%u7535%u538B%u5E76%u8BA1%u7B97%u529F%u7387"},{"question":". %u4EE5%u4E0B%u54EA%u9879%u5173%u4E8E%u4E0B%u56FE%u4E3B%u63A7%u6A21%u5757%u5C4F%u5E55%u663E%u793A%u7684%u5185%u5BB9%u63CF%u8FF0%u6B63%u786E%u7684%u662F%uFF1F<img src=\"http://hz-platinic-data-prod.oss-cn-hangzhou.aliyuncs.com/3dacdcd0-3e9c-4613-83a3-8c19ed3c586b\">","answer":"%u4E3B%u63A7%u6A21%u5757%u7248%u672C%u53F7%u6700%u540E%u4E00%u4F4D%u4E3A0"},{"question":". %u7535%u6E90%u7BA1%u7406%u6A21%u5757%u9ED1%u8272%u822A%u7A7A%u63D2%u5934%u53EF%u4EE5%u8FDE%u63A5%u54EA%u4E2A%u6A21%u5757%uFF1F","answer":"%u4E3B%u63A7%u6A21%u5757"},{"question":". %u5B89%u88C5%u540E%uFF0C%u573A%u5730%u4EA4%u4E92%u6A21%u5757%u82E5%u6709%u6548%u68C0%u6D4B%u8DDD%u79BB%u8F83%u7406%u8BBA%u503C%u6709%u6240%u7F29%u77ED%uFF0C%u6709%u53EF%u80FD%u51FA%u73B0%u7684%u60C5%u51B5%u4E3A%uFF1F<br>%u2460%u5E26RoboMaster%u56FE%u6807%u9762%u88AB%u94DD%u677F%u906E%u6321<br>%u2461%u5E26RoboMaster%u56FE%u6807%u9762%u88AB%u78B3%u7EA4%u677F%u906E%u6321<br>%u2462%u5E26RoboMaster%u56FE%u6807%u9762%u88AB%u4E9A%u514B%u529B%u677F%u906E%u6321<br>%u2463%u5E26RoboMaster%u56FE%u6807%u9762%u88AB%u6728%u677F%u906E%u6321","answer":"%u2460%u2461"},{"question":". %u5728%u7535%u6E90%u7BA1%u7406%u6A21%u5757%u4E2D%uFF0C%u4EE5%u4E0B%u8BF4%u6CD5%u9519%u8BEF%u7684%u662F%u54EA%u4E2A%uFF1F","answer":"%u7535%u6E90%u7BA1%u7406%u6A21%u5757%u6B63%u5E38%u8FDE%u63A5%u81F3%u4E3B%u63A7%u6A21%u5757%u65F6%uFF0CLink%u706F%u5E38%u4EAE%u3002"},{"question":". %u7EC4%u5EFA%u5C40%u57DF%u7F51%u65F6%uFF0C%u4EE5%u4E0B%u63CF%u8FF0%u4E0D%u6B63%u786E%u7684%u662F%uFF1F","answer":"%u5F00%u542F%u673A%u5668%u4EBA%u7535%u6E90%u7ED9%u88C1%u5224%u7CFB%u7EDF%u4F9B%u7535%u3002%u5C06%u4E3B%u63A7%u6A21%u5757IP%u8BBE%u7F6E%u6210192.168.1.20~192.168.1.230%u4E2D%u7684%u4EFB%u610FIP"},{"question":". %u4EE5%u4E0B%u9009%u9879%u4E2D%uFF0C%u5173%u4E8E%u4E3B%u63A7%u6A21%u5757%u4E2D%u8C03%u8BD5%u529F%u80FD%u63CF%u8FF0%u4E0D%u6B63%u786E%u7684%u662F%uFF1F","answer":"%u8C03%u8BD5%u529F%u80FD%u9875%u9762\"Debug Option\"%u5C5E%u4E8E\"Game Setup\"%u5B50%u9879%u76EE"},{"question":". %u56FE%u4F20%u6A21%u5757%u53D1%u5C04%u7AEF%u4E0E%u56FE%u4F20%u6A21%u5757%u63A5%u6536%u7AEF%u9700%u8981%u901A%u8FC7 ID %u5339%u914D%u624D%u80FD%u6B63%u786E%u4F20%u8F93%u89C6%u9891%u56FE%u50CF%u3002%u5728%u65E5%u5E38%u8C03%u8BD5%u4E2D%uFF0C%u4EE5%u4E0B%u5BF9%u5E94%u5173%u7CFB%u6B63%u786E%u7684%u662F%uFF1F<br>%u2460%u673A%u5668%u4EBAID%u4E3ARED1%uFF0C%u76F8%u673A%u56FE%u4F20%u6A21%u5757%u63A5%u6536%u7AEFID%u4E3A1<br>%u2461%u673A%u5668%u4EBAID%u4E3ABLUE1%uFF0C%u76F8%u673A%u56FE%u4F20%u6A21%u5757%u63A5%u6536%u7AEFID%u4E3A1<br>%u2462%u673A%u5668%u4EBAID%u4E3ABLUE4%uFF0C%u76F8%u673A%u56FE%u4F20%u6A21%u5757%u63A5%u6536%u7AEFID%u4E3A3<br>%u2463%u673A%u5668%u4EBAID%u4E3ABLUE2%uFF0C%u76F8%u673A%u56FE%u4F20%u6A21%u5757%u63A5%u6536%u7AEFID%u4E3A2","answer":"%u2460%u2462"},{"question":". %u8FD0%u884CRoboMaster Server%u7A0B%u5E8F%u7684%u7535%u8111%u9700%u8981%u5BF9%u5176IP%u5730%u5740%u8FDB%u884C%u4EE5%u4E0B%u54EA%u4E00%u9879%u8BBE%u7F6E","answer":"%u5C06IP%u5730%u5740%u8BBE%u7F6E%u4E3A192.168.1.2"},{"question":". %u4E0B%u5217%u5173%u4E8E%u5347%u7EA7%u5DE5%u5177%u7684%u4F7F%u7528%u63CF%u8FF0%u9519%u8BEF%u4E00%u9879%u7684%u662F","answer":"%u5347%u7EA7%u5DE5%u5177%u4E00%u6B21%u53EA%u80FD%u7ED9%u540C%u4E00%u4E2A%u6A21%u5757%u8FDB%u884C%u5347%u7EA7"},{"question":". %u88C1%u5224%u7CFB%u7EDF%u7528%u6237%u63A5%u53E3%u63CF%u8FF0%u6B63%u786E%u7684%u662F%uFF1F<br>%u2460%u901A%u8FC7UART%u8F93%u51FA%uFF0C%u6CE2%u7279%u7387%u4E3A115200<br>%u2461%u88C1%u5224%u7CFB%u7EDF%u7528%u6237%u63A5%u53E3%u5904%u4E8E%u4E3B%u63A7%u6A21%u5757%u4E0A<br>%u2462%u88C1%u5224%u7CFB%u7EDF%u7528%u6237%u63A5%u53E3%u5904%u4E8E%u7535%u6E90%u7BA1%u7406%u6A21%u5757%u4E0A<br>%u2463%u4E00%u5171%u6709%u4E24%u8DEF%u88C1%u5224%u7CFB%u7EDF%u7528%u6237%u63A5%u53E3%uFF0C%u4E00%u4E2A%u5904%u4E8E%u4E3B%u63A7%u6A21%u5757%u4E0A%uFF0C%u53E6%u4E00%u4E2A%u5904%u4E8E%u7535%u6E90%u7BA1%u7406%u6A21%u5757%u4E0A","answer":"%u2460%u2462"},{"question":". %u4EE5%u4E0B%u5173%u4E8E%u4E0B%u56FE%u4E3B%u63A7%u6A21%u5757%u5C4F%u5E55%u663E%u793A%u7684%u5185%u5BB9%u63CF%u8FF0%u6B63%u786E%u7684%u662F%uFF1F<br>%u2460%u673A%u5668%u4EBA%u7AEF%u672A%u767B%u5F55%u5230%u670D%u52A1%u5668<br>%u2461%u673A%u5668%u4EBA%u5DF2%u7ECF%u63A5%u5165%u65E0%u7EBF%u7F51%u7EDC<br>%u2462%u4E3B%u63A7%u6A21%u5757%u6E29%u5EA6%u5F02%u5E38<br>%u246342mm%u6D4B%u901F%u6A21%u5757%u5904%u4E8E%u79BB%u7EBF%u72B6%u6001<img src=\"http://hz-platinic-data-prod.oss-cn-hangzhou.aliyuncs.com/f8330cd6-74aa-4d55-8d8d-510028d01282\">","answer":"%u2460%u2461"},{"question":". %u88C1%u5224%u7CFB%u7EDF%u5404%u6A21%u5757%u6B63%u5E38%u5DE5%u4F5C%uFF0C%u662F%u4FDD%u8BC1%u6BD4%u8D5B%u516C%u5E73%u516C%u6B63%u7684%u524D%u63D0%u6761%u4EF6%u3002%u56E0%u6B64%uFF0C%u673A%u5668%u4EBA%u7AEF%u5728%u4E0A%u7535%u542F%u52A8%u4E4B%u540E%uFF0C%u4F1A%u5BF9%u5404%u4E2A%u6A21%u5757%u8FDB%u884C%u81EA%u68C0%u3002%u91CD%u8981%u6A21%u5757%u81EA%u68C0%u4E0D%u901A%u8FC7%u65F6%uFF0C%u706F%u6761%u6A21%u5757%u4F1A%u5448%u4EC0%u4E48%u989C%u8272%uFF1F","answer":"%u9EC4%u8272"},{"question":". %u5728%u88C1%u5224%u7CFB%u7EDF%u670D%u52A1%u5668%u754C%u9762%u60F3%u8981%u8FDB%u5165%u8F6F%u4EF6%u5E2E%u52A9%u9875%u9762%u9700%u8981%u6267%u884C%u4EE5%u4E0B%u90A3%u4E00%u9879%u64CD%u4F5C","answer":"%u6CA1%u6709%u8FD9%u4E00%u529F%u80FD"},{"question":". %u88C1%u5224%u7CFB%u7EDF%u7684%u4EBA%u673A%u4EA4%u4E92%u63A5%u53E3%uFF0C%u662F%u7531%u4E00%u5757%u663E%u793A%u5C4F%u53CA%u56DB%u4E2A%u6309%u952E%u7EC4%u6210%u3002%u5982%u4E0B%u56FE%u6240%u793A%uFF0C%u5BF9%u6807%u6CE8%u63CF%u8FF0%u6B63%u786E%u7684%u662F%uFF1F<img src=\"http://hz-platinic-data-prod.oss-cn-hangzhou.aliyuncs.com/31e6bb97-333f-463d-b414-f8a7a314cfce\">","answer":"1.%u786E%u8BA4 2.%u53D6%u6D88 3.%u4E0A%u7FFB 4.%u4E0B%u7FFB "},{"question":". %u901A%u8FC7%u4EA4%u4E92%u754C%u9762%u53EF%u4EE5%u67E5%u770B%u673A%u5668%u4EBA%u7AEF%u5F53%u524D%u8FDE%u63A5%u7684WiFi%u4FE1%u606F%uFF0C%u4E0B%u9762%u63CF%u8FF0%u6B63%u786E%u7684%u662F<br>%u2460%u67E5%u770BWiFi%u4FE1%u606F%u7684%u9009%u9879%u540D%u5B57%u4E3A\"Connect Information\"%uFF0C%u5C5E%u4E8EGame Setup%u5B50%u83DC%u5355<br>%u2461%u901A%u4FD7%u5730%u8BF4%uFF0CSSID%u4FBF%u662F%u4F60%u7ED9%u81EA%u5DF1%u7684%u65E0%u7EBF%u7F51%u7EDC%u6240%u53D6%u7684%u540D%u5B57%uFF0C%u5728%u67E5%u8BE2WiFi%u4FE1%u606F%u9875%u9762%u53EF%u4EE5%u8BFB%u53D6%u5F53%u524D%u8FDE%u63A5%u7684AP%u7684SSID<br>%u2462%u4E3A%u4E86%u907F%u514D%u5FD8%u8BB0%u65E0%u7EBF%u7F51%u7EDC%u7684%u5BC6%u7801%uFF0C%u5728%u67E5%u8BE2WiFi%u4FE1%u606F%u9875%u9762%u80FD%u8BFB%u53D6%u65E0%u7EBF%u7F51%u7EDC%u7684%u5BC6%u7801<br>%u2463%u4FE1%u53F7%u5F3A%u5EA6%u4FE1%u53F7%u8D28%u91CF%u80FD%u53CD%u9988%u5F53%u524D%u7684%u65E0%u7EBF%u94FE%u8DEF%u7A33%u5B9A%u6027%u3001%u65E0%u7EBF%u7F51%u7EDC&amp;%u4E3B%u63A7%u6A21%u5757%u7684%u65E0%u7EBF%u8D28%u91CF%u548C%u8DDD%u79BB%u8FDC%u8FD1%uFF0C%u5728%u67E5%u8BE2WiFi%u4FE1%u606F%u9875%u9762%u80FD%u8BFB%u5230%u8FD9%u4E24%u4E2A%u4FE1%u606F","answer":"%u2461%u2463"},{"question":". %u4E3B%u63A7%u6A21%u5757%u4E2D%u786E%u8BA4%u952E%u957F%u6309%u7684%u64CD%u4F5C%u4E0D%u591A%uFF0C%u4F46%u90FD%u662F%u6BD4%u8F83%u91CD%u8981%u800C%u4E14%u5BB9%u6613%u88AB%u5FFD%u7565%u7684%u529F%u80FD%uFF0C%u4E0B%u9762%u5BF9%u786E%u8BA4%u952E%u957F%u6309%u63CF%u8FF0%u7684%u529F%u80FD%u6B63%u786E%u7684%u662F%uFF1F<br>%u2460%u5728%u4E3B%u9875%u9762%u4E2D%u786E%u8BA4%u952E%u957F%u6309%u53EF%u4EE5%u8FDB%u5165%u673A%u5668%u4EBA%u529F%u80FD%u9875%u9762<br>%u2461%u5728%u8FDE%u63A5%u5BF9%u5E94%u7684SSID%u65F6%uFF0C%u786E%u8BA4%u952E%u957F%u6309%u53EF%u4EE5%u8BB0%u4F4F%u8BE5SSID%uFF0C%u91CD%u65B0%u4E0A%u7535%u4F1A%u81EA%u52A8%u8FDE%u63A5%u8BE5SSID<br>%u2462%u5728%u5B9E%u65F6%u4FE1%u606F%u663E%u793A%u9875%u9762%u786E%u8BA4%u952E%u957F%u6309%u53EF%u4EE5%u8FDB%u5165%u673A%u5668%u4EBA%u529F%u80FD%u9875%u9762","answer":"%u2460%u2461%u2462"},{"question":". %u4EE5%u4E0B%u6A21%u5757%u4E2D%u4E0D%u80FD%u548C%u6D4B%u901F%u6A21%u5757%u4E32%u8054%u7684%u662F%u54EA%u4E2A?","answer":"%u4E3B%u63A7%u6A21%u5757"},{"question":". %u73B0%u5728%u9700%u8981%u5C06%u673A%u5668%u8BBE%u7F6E%u6210%u79BB%u7EBF%u6A21%u5F0F%uFF0C%u4E0B%u9762%u6B63%u786E%u7684%u8BBE%u7F6E%u987A%u5E8F%u5E94%u8BE5%u662F%uFF1F<br>a.%u4E3B%u9875%u9762%u957F%u6309%u786E%u8BA4%u952E%uFF0C%u901A%u8FC7%u4E0A%u7FFB%u4E0B%u7FFB%u6309%u952E%u9009%u62E9\"Debug Option\"%uFF0C%u77ED%u6309%u786E%u8BA4%u952E%u8FDB%u5165<br>b.%u901A%u8FC7%u4E0A%u7FFB%u4E0B%u7FFB%u6309%u952E%u9009%u62E9\"Function Enable Mask\"%uFF0C%u77ED%u6309%u786E%u8BA4%u952E%u8FDB%u5165<br>c.%u901A%u8FC7%u4E0A%u7FFB%u4E0B%u7FFB%u6309%u952E%u9009%u62E9\"Offline Mode\"%uFF0C%u77ED%u6309%u786E%u8BA4%u952E%u7FFB%u8F6C%u79BB%u7EBF%u6A21%u5F0F%uFF0C%u786E%u4FDD%u540E%u9762%u65B9%u6846%u6253%u4E0A%u52FE%u53F7","answer":"ac"},{"question":". %u82E5%u60F3%u7EC4%u5EFARoboMaster%u88C1%u5224%u7CFB%u7EDF%u5C40%u57DF%u7F51%uFF0C%u9700%u8981%u5C06%u65E0%u7EBFAP%u7684SSDI%u548C%u5BC6%u7801%u8BBE%u7F6E%u4E3A%u4EE5%u4E0B%u54EA%u4E00%u9879","answer":"SSID%uFF1A%u4EFB%u610F%u540D%u79F0\n%u5BC6%u7801%uFF1A12345678"},{"question":". %u5728%u4F7F%u7528%u5347%u7EA7%u5DE5%u5177%u7ED9%u88C5%u7532%u6A21%u5757%u8FDB%u884C%u5347%u7EA7%u65F6%uFF0C%u53D1%u73B0%u5347%u7EA7%u5DE5%u5177%u65E0%u6CD5%u6B63%u786E%u663E%u793A%u88C5%u7532%u6A21%u5757%u7684%u6570%u91CF%uFF0C%u5E76%u4E14%u88C5%u7532%u6A21%u5757%u6307%u793A%u706F%u5448%u7EA2%u3001%u84DD%u3001%u7D2B%u4E09%u8272%u4EA4%u66FF%u95EA%u70C1%u72B6%u6001%uFF0C%u5219%u53EF%u80FD%u662F%u4EE5%u4E0B%u54EA%u4E00%u79CD%u539F%u56E0%u5BFC%u81F4%u7684","answer":"%u88C5%u7532%u6A21%u5757ID%u51B2%u7A81"},{"question":". %u4E3B%u63A7%u6A21%u5757%u5E94%u8BE5%u8FDE%u63A5%u5230%u7535%u6E90%u7BA1%u7406%u6A21%u5757%u7684%u54EA%u4E2A%u63A5%u53E3%u4E0A%uFF1F<img src=\"http://hz-platinic-data-prod.oss-cn-hangzhou.aliyuncs.com/0c608776-404f-4aa8-aefe-d27ace8e0743\">","answer":"1"}]